

Parvindra Tongar (UI/UX Designer)

User Experience | User-Centered Design | Interaction Design | Startups | Figma, Sketch | Prototypes, Wireframes, User-flow | HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap | Responsive Web Design

CONTACT

Mobile: +91-7428098010 Email: parvtongar@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Post Graduation (2009)

Aptech ACCP(Web Design and Development)

Graduation (2007)

Bachelor of Arts (CCS University)

PROFILE SUMMARY

User Experience Designer with **10+ years** of experience in interaction design working with startups. Follow a quick approach to design and go live within a short period of time.

I have experience in Web Application, Admin Panels and Mobile-based designs from paper sketch to interconnect screens prototypes.

PROJECTS

CurrencyEx, 12 Weeks

An application that allowed for business-to-business foreign currency and same-currency payments

MovTek, 24 Weeks

MovTek provides Air and Sea Freight services across the globe.

Hire Military Jobs, 24 Weeks

This project helps Retired Military persons to find jobs in corporate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2016 to Present

Lead Designer at Nuage Biztech pvt Itd

I have worked on multi-domain Web and Mobile Apps. have versatile experience in Designing Admin Panels, Web Apps and Websites.

May 2013 to Oct 2015

Website Designer at Rati software solutions

Website Designer, Responsive Design, Web Designer, HTML Coder, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.

Aug 2008 to May 2013

Website Designer at ekant solutions

Website Designer, Web Designer, HTML5, CSS3, Slicing - Photoshop to HTML.